bookmarkall.com 2011-06-26

# BookmarkAll Service Security and Privacy Policies

Security and Privacy Policies  

* * *

|   
---  
Security  
What this BookmarkAll.com family privacy policy covers  
What information we collect  
How your personal information is protected  
What cookies are and how we use them  
How you can update or change your information  
Children's privacy  
Linked sites  
How to contact us  
Revisions to this privacy policy  

Security Our Secure Server Module encrypts your password before saving it to the database, protecting your identify data collected when you create, update, log into your account from unauthorized access.  
Back to Top  
  
Privacy Policy

What this BookmarkAll family privacy policy covers 

The BookmarkAll Family includes bookmarkall.com; bookmarkprofile.com; bookmarkprofiles.com.

This Privacy Policy outlines BookmarkAll Family practices regarding information collected (a) online at www.BookmarkAll.com platform (b) online at the bookmarkprofile.com, bookmarkpfrofiles.com Web sites, any Web site operated by BookmarkAll Family members; 

We suggest that you review this Privacy Policy periodically as we may update it from time to time. This policy was last revised on August 01, 2006. By visiting a BookmarkAll Family Site or otherwise interacting with an BookmarkAll Family member, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.   
  
Back to Top  
  
What information we collect Each time you visit a BookmarkAll Site the Web server automatically collects your Internet service provider's address, the Web page from which you came, Web browser software, and a record of your activity while visiting the site. 

The BookmarkAll Family members collect personally identifiable information (such as first and last name, home address, email address and telephone number) that you provide when you register; visit the BookmarkAll Sites; create or edit your Registries ; participate in a contest or sweepstakes promotion; fill out a survey or questionnaire; sign up for a survey; contact an BookmarkAll Family member (by e-mail or otherwise); contact BookmarkAll Family customer service representatives; or otherwise interact with a BookmarkAll Family member. The information you provide to BookmarkAll Family members may also be combined with demographic and other information that is publicly available in order to allow the BookmarkAll Family members to better communicate with you. 

For purposes of this policy, information regarding your children that you (the parent) provide to the BookmarkAll Family is treated in the same manner as information collected about you.   
  
Back to Top  
  
Protecting your personal informationYour personal information is used only by the BookmarkAll Family members to enhance your guest relationship with them, respond to your requests, tailor offerings to you and communicate with you about products, services, special offerings, and events or programs offered by the BookmarkAll Family members or their marketing partners that may be of interest to you. The BookmarkAll Family may also use this information to analyze and manage its businesses. Aggregate data (which does not allow an individual to be identified, contacted, or located) is collected from online and offline facilities and may be used to enhance the ability of the BookmarkAll Family members to communicate with you and for internal analysis and management purposes. 

BookmarkAll Family members will not license, sell, or provide your personal information to any unaffiliated third party except as permitted by this policy or with your consent.   
  
Back to Top  
  
What cookies are and how we use them The BookmarkAll Sites (and Online Stores) use "cookies" which are small pieces of information stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. The cookies are used to connect your computer with information stored about your preferences. (Some examples of this data include your account preferences, items added to your shopping cart, user-specific information on pages accessed and previous visits to the site.) BookmarkAll Family members do not use cookies to store any of your personal or financial information on your computer. If you reject cookies, you may not be able to participate in certain activities or receive a presentation tailored to you.   
Back to Top  
  
How you can update or change your personal information  If at any time you want to update or change your personal information on any other BookmarkAll Site, you can opt out of receiving online communications.  
Back to Top  
  
Children's Privacy  The Online Stores and the BookmarkAll Sites do not knowingly solicit or collect personally identifiable information online from children under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. If any BookmarkAll Family Member learns that a child under the age of 13 has submitted personally identifiable information online, in contravention of these measures, it will take all reasonable measures to delete such information from its databases and to not use such information for any purpose except where necessary to protect the safety of the child or others or as required by law.   
Back to Top  
  
Linked sites  The BookmarkAll Sites and Online Stores may contain links to other sites including content from that is occasionally framed within a BookmarkAll Site or the Online Stores. Please note that the privacy policies at these other sites may be different from this one. You should review the privacy policy of any site linked to or framed within an BookmarkAll Site or the Online Stores prior to providing any information on or to that site.   
Back to Top  
  
How to contact us  If you have questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please send an e-mail to support@bookmarkall.com   
Back to Top  
  
Revisions to this privacy policy  This Privacy Policy may be updated and revised from time to time and we will post any changes on this policy. You agree that the information that we gather now will be subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use. We may contact you with periodic notices concerning our Privacy Policy but you should check the BookmarkAll Sites periodically to review any changes. 

Effective Date of Privacy Policy: July 20, 2004   
  
Back to Top
